bollywoodheaven.com 2005-12-14

# Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement for Bollywood Heaven 

**Bollywood Heaven** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [Bollywood Heaven ](http://www.bollywoodheaven.com/)

#### Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

#### Advertisers 

We use an outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

#### Personal Information 

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

#### External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Bollywood Heaven** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

#### Special Relationships 

All of the following services are hosted and maintained externally by the below listed providers.

All information held by [Webring.org](http://www.webring.org/), [Listbot](http://www.listbot.com/) & [Everyone.net](http://www.everyone.net/) is provided by the users themselves and is used by **Bollywood Heaven** for administration purposes ONLY. 

Email addresses held with [Listbot](http://www.listbot.com/) are used for emailing all members of the mailing list of any site updates/information, any details held will under no circumstances be provided to a 3rd party.

Webring provided by [Webring.org](http://www.webring.org/). Mailing List provided by [Listbot](http://www.listbot.com/). Hit counters [NetStat](http://usa.nedstatbasic.net/), [Linkexchange](http://www.linkexchange.com/) & [Hitbox](http://www.hitbox.com/). Email & BBS by [Everyone.net](http://www.everyone.net/). Site search [Freefind.com](http://www.freefind.com/). Horoscopes by [Vantagenet.com](http://www.vantagenet.com/). Music Heaven by [Indiahits](http://www.indiahits.com/). Chat Heaven 1 & 2 Java chat by [Multichat](http://www.multichat.com/) & [Xoom](http://www.xoom.com/).

#### Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

#### Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

* * *
